Guide to the G. Evelyn Hutchinson Papers Relating to Rebecca West
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Clippings, 1922-1987; Series IV; 1.6; (4 boxes)
  - WORKS BY REBECCA WEST
    - Articles
      - "G" general, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 250)
      - "I" general, 1948-77 (Box 10, Folder 251)
      - "J-L" general, 1930-65, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 252)
      - "M" general, 1947-82 (Box 10, Folder 253)
      - "N-O" general, 1949-72, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 254)
        See also: Oversize, Box 14, folder 324
      - "R" general, 1955-71, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 255-257)
        See also: Oversize, Box 14, folders 325-326
      - "S" general, 1951-75, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 258)
        See also: Oversize, Box 14, folder 327
      - "T" general, 1925-77, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 259-260)
      - "U-V" general, 1963-76, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 261-262)
      - "W" general, 1916-71 (Box 11, Folder 263-264)
    - Book reviews
      - "A" general, 1938-79 (Box 11, Folder 265)
        See also: Oversize, Box 14, folder 328
      - "B" general, 1931-82, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 266)
      - "C" general, 1961-72, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 267)
      - "D" general, 1962-80, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 268)
      - "E" general, 1961-79 (Box 11, Folder 269)
      - "F" general, 1962-78, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 270)
      - "G" general, 1963-83, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 271)
      - "H" general, 1943-81, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 272)
      - "I-K" general, 1964-77, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 273)
      - "L" general, 1955-81, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 273a)
      - "M" general, 1949-81, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 274)
      - "N" general, 1961-78, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 275)
      - "O" general, 1961-81, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 276)
      - "P" general, 1963-82, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 277)
      - "Q-R" general, 1961-73 (Box 12, Folder 278)
      - "S" general, 1937-80, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 279-281)
        See also: Oversize, Box 14, folder 329
      - "T" general, 1948-78, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 282)
      - "U" general, 1962-79 (Box 12, Folder 283)
      - "V" general, 1962-79, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 284)
      - "W" general, 1961-82, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 285)
      - "Y" general, 1976, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 286)
    - Other Writings
      - "Deliverance"
        - Argosy Magazine, 1953 May (Box 12, Folder 287)
        - Ladies' Home Journal, n.d.
          See: Oversize, Box 14, folder 330
        - Suspense, 1959 Jul (Box 12, Folder 288)
      - Letters to the Editor, 1928-80, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 289-290)
  - WORKS ABOUT REBECCA WEST
    - Profiles and Interviews
      - Articles, 1948-68 (Box 12, Folder 291)
        See also: Oversize, Box 14, folder 331
      - Articles, 1970-77 (Box 12, Folder 292-294)
        See also: Oversize, Box 14, folder 332
      - Articles, 1978-87 (Box 12, Folder 295-296)
    - Reviews of Books by West
      - The Birds Fall Down, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 297)
      - The Court and the Castle, 1957-58 (Box 12, Folder 298-299)
        See also: Oversize, Box 14, folder 333
      - The Fountain Overflows, 1956-57 (Box 13, Folder 300)
        See also: Oversize, Box 14, folder 334
      - The Judge, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 301)
      - The Meaning of Treason, 1947-49 (Box 13, Folder 302)
      - The New Meaning of Treason, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 303)
      - This Real Night, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 304)
      - A Train of Powder, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 305)
        See also: Oversize, Box 14, folder 335
      - The Young Rebecca and 1900, [1982] (Box 13, Folder 306)
    - Reviews of Books about West
      - Glendinning, Victoria, Rebecca West: A Life, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 307)
      - Ray, Gordon N., H. G. Wells and Rebecca West, 1974-75, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 308-311)
      - Wilson, Angus, Rebecca West: A Celebration, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 312)
      - Wolfe, Peter, Rebecca West: Artist and Thinker, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 313)
    - Brief Mentions
      - Articles, 1938-83, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 314-318)
        See also: Oversize, Box 14, folder 336-337
- Oversize, 1938-82; 1.5; (1 box)
  Oversize contains oversize material arranged in series order.
  - WRITINGS OF REBECCA WEST
    - "Kafka and the Mystery of Bureaucracy", corrected galley proof, 1957 Jul 25 (Box 14, Folder 319)
  - CLIPPINGS: WORKS BY REBECCA WEST
    - Articles
      - "A" general, 1953-74, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 320-321)
      - "C" general, 1950-61, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 322)
      - "F" general, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 323)
      - "N" general, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 324)
      - "R" general, 1955, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 325-326)
      - "S" general, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 327)
    - Book Reviews
      - "A" general, 1938, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 328)
      - "S" general, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 329)
    - Other Writings
      - "Deliverance", n.d. (Box 14, Folder 330)
  - WORKS ABOUT REBECCA WEST
    - Profiles and Interviews
      - Articles, 1953-77 (Box 14, Folder 331-332)
    - Reviews of Books by West
      - The Court and the Castle, 1957-58 (Box 14, Folder 333)
      - The Fountain Overflows, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 334)
      - A Train of Powder, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 335)
    - Brief Mentions
      - Articles, 1944-82, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 336-338)
- Restricted Fragile Papers
  Box 15, Restricted Fragile Papers, contains fragile originals. The material is arranged in folder order and may only be seen with the permission of the appropriate curator.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 1 (Box 15, Folder 339)
  - Box 1, folder 2 (Box 15, Folder 340)
  - Box 1, folder 3 (Box 15, Folder 341)
  - Box 1, folder 8 (Box 15, Folder 342)
  - Box 1, folder 9 (Box 15, Folder 343)
  - Box 1, folder 10 (Box 15, Folder 344)
  - Box 1, folder 13 (Box 15, Folder 345)
  - Box 1, folder 22 (Box 15, Folder 346)
  - Box 1, folder 23 (Box 15, Folder 347)
  - Box 1, folder 26 (Box 15, Folder 348)
  - Box 1, folder 29 (Box 15, Folder 349)
  - Box 4, folder 101 (Box 15, Folder 350)
  - Box 4, folder 104 (Box 15, Folder 351)
  - Box 4, folder 105 (Box 15, Folder 352)
  - Box 4, folder 107 (Box 15, Folder 353)
  - Box 4, folder 117 (Box 15, Folder 354)
  - Box 4, folder 119 (Box 15, Folder 355)
  - Box 4, folder 127 (Box 15, Folder 356)
  - Box 4, folder 132 (Box 15, Folder 357)
  - Box 4, folder 133 (Box 15, Folder 358)
  - Box 4, folder 135 (Box 15, Folder 359)
  - Box 5, folder 168 (Box 15, Folder 360)
  - Box 6, folder 177 (Box 15, Folder 361)
  - Box 7, folder 208 (Box 15, Folder 362)
  - Box 7, folder 209 (Box 15, Folder 363)
  - Box 9, folder 219 (Box 15, Folder 364)
  - Box 9, folder 232 (Box 15, Folder 365)
  - Box 9, folder 235 (Box 15, Folder 366)
  - Box 9, folder 240 (Box 15, Folder 367)
  - Box 9, folder 242 (Box 15, Folder 368)
  - Box 11, folder 258 (Box 15, Folder 369)
  - Box 11, folder 271 (Box 15, Folder 370)
  - Box 11, folder 272 (Box 15, Folder 371)
  - Box 11, folder 274 (Box 15, Folder 372)
  - Box 13, folder 314 (Box 15, Folder 373)